Yeah, I just hate this guy I'm about to yap about. He's a degenerate streamer that no one really watches in the first place.
His career is a bigger flop than the new Snow White movie.
And apparently he's been banned numerous times from basically every streaming platform,
but he keeps crawling his way back like the little roach that he is.
And even though he's a public nuisance that's perpetually goober-maxing,
he doesn't even really have a community of people that follow him ironically.
Typically with a special specimen like this, there will be people that tune in just to watch all
the madness unfold and point and laugh at the guy. But he doesn't even have that because he is
just so unbelievably lame. He's such a colossal loser that it's not even fun to watch him ruin
his life. Like you get more entertainment out of a knock-knock joke than tuning into this guy's
streams. He's a pile of shit that not even mosquitoes will fly around and there is an endless
supply of things you can easily shoot spitballs at when it comes to this guy. But there's one in
particular that I want to focus on and the whole reason I'm making this. How often and how
proudly he abuses his dog on stream.
The richest thing is she gave me a fuck.
I imagine this brain dead moron can't spell the word context but I already know in defense of
this clip you would try and point to the longer version for the full scoop because you're only
taking a snippet of it. It's out of context. Even though there's really no amount of context
that justifies hitting your dog and making the dog yelp in pain and then forcefully dragging it
back into the room to throw onto your chair. But if you want the full version of this clip which
is also equally hard to watch and also still paints a very bad picture of this piece of shit
I'll go ahead and show you that too. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Peaches.
Don't throw this. Gritchest thing is she gave me a fuck.
This is my fucking dog.
I'm your fuck. Stay. Hey. Stop. Stay.
This is my fucking dog. I don't get fuck. You're not taking my dog away from me.
I don't get fuck. I don't get fuck. You're not taking my fucking dog away from me.
She's a fucking dog. Stay. Stay.
I don't get fuck. You're not taking my fucking dog away from me. I don't get fuck.
The girl in the clip is trying to calm this raging dork down and try and remove the dog from a
dangerous situation here from him and he continues to fucking fiefive foe from his way around there
and forcefully grabbing the dog and slamming it onto his chair which again causes the dog to scream
and pain and try and run away and terror from this menace and I am pretty sure he tries to paint
this as like a oh I just love my dog and she was trying to separate me from my dog. This bitch
is trying to take my dog. You won't take my dog away from me. My beloved pet that I cherish
which is a bunch of dirty barnacles. He made the dog cry multiple times here. The girl even points
out like stop hitting the dog and then at the end of that clip he does like try and rub the dog's
chest after he has slammed the dog onto that chair multiple times. He needs to have this dog
removed from him. This is not fair to that animal at all. I'm literally gonna fucking kill this dog, bro.
This is not good. You better come there. If you ever actually hit the 40-grower, now it's done bit.
Fuck it.
Get it off.
You have to rest her fucking life. She's standing there for rest her fucking life.
Fuck off that. I've literally just standing there forever. Fuck that dog.
I hope she fucking cries. I hope she fucking wants to commit suicide at that dog bit.
I hope you jump off her fucking balcony.
Fuck it.
Wow, yeah, you can really feel the love.
Regular old John Wick here with the amount that he cares for this animal.
What a sane human being this is. It's fucking unhinged, man. In so many clips, this girl is
constantly trying to get him to stop hitting the dog and stop like being really mean to the dog
and like locking it up and threatening it.
I will fucking kill you in front of everyone right here. I will fucking kill you.
Right now, I will fucking kill you right here. I'm fucking everyone.
I will fucking kill you.
Hey? I will fucking kill you right here.
I will break your fucking neck right here.
See the fucking.
I got a heartache on this dog. I literally will kill this dog.
See you guys in private. This is their fucking suit.
Wait, how?
You want your water?
Fuck this stupid dog. I hope you can fuck this.
Sit.
Just look at some of these messages in his chat from these loveless,
dickless, humunculi. They get so excited every time he starts to talk about killing his dog or
when he starts hitting his dog.
So like this first one, peaches need to be strangled.
That's his dog's name.
Clearly not a service dog.
Beat that dumb service dog up.
Bad dumb dog.
Like what the fuck?
He is addicted to talking to his dog like it's a legal legends ranked game.
Like this kind of shit here he tries to downplay as like not being super serious and the community
tries to dilute themselves into thinking that he's just trolling.
But I think it's pretty clear he does mean these things.
He actively hits his dog.
I think it's pretty clear we have a lot of evidence to indicate that he means this vile
shit that he's spouting about his dog.
I am also very shocked that he even used that nomenclature community to describe what he has.
Because that's not what he has.
He has like four people that tune in occasionally and make like one message in chat every 10 minutes.
Like you can see it for yourself.
The proof is in the pudding.
Somehow this brain dead worm thought it'd be a good idea to post his dead chat on screen.
And that shit is not moving.
That's going at a glacial pace.
You're seeing more activity on Yahoo Answers than you will in one of his streams.
And Yahoo Answers has been shut down buried in the dirt for like nine years.
I cannot believe that he even puts that up there on his own accord.
So he doesn't really have a viewer base or anything like that.
But it doesn't matter.
I couldn't help but talk about this guy because this is just infuriating.
And I haven't seen another streamer so proudly just abuse their pet on stream like this.
It's craziness.
Give it up.
He is a pillow and a borderline personality.
She is like only use me blades.
And then he's feeling she is bad news.
Shut up.
If you don't shut your mouth.
Okay.
I'll be bad.
You'll just be bad.
It'll be bad.
Shut up.
This isn't all of them but I don't think there's any need to show you more.
This kind of thing is just heartbreaking.
That dog seems like such a sweetheart that does not deserve to have an owner like this.
No dog does.
This shit is just so foul.
And another thing I'll do is he'll hit the dog really hard.
He'll hit peaches hard as fuck and then very lightly like a like in that first clip where he was
sleeping.
In fact, most of the clips you can find of this guy are sleeping on stream.
That's like the main thing he does is just fucking hibernate and hope people will donate while he's asleep.
But anyway, you saw him lean over and just clawber peaches on the on the snout and then lightly tap
peaches on the head.
And then he even had the gall to make a gesture up like up here to try and invite peaches to come
sleep on his chest.
It's crazy how often and how proudly he does this shit.
And even more crazy that there's like six or seven weirdos that'll watch and cheer him on
encouraging the behavior.
And I imagine that's a big motivator for this guy.
He'll just bring peaches on stream threatened to kill the dog and hit the dog quite a bit
and get some cheers and applause from these absolute fucking vermin that are watching him.
But like I said, most of his clips that you'll find are him sleeping.
That seems to be like the bulk of what he does is just go to sleep while filming it.
But his most popular clip isn't from his snooze in streams.
It's actually from him threatening to shoot some kids like inviting them out so he can shoot them.
All right, bro, what's the back there?
I'm from Toronto kid, pull up.
You're a little ass gun that you never shot in your life.
Put that, show me the bullet.
No man.
Exactly, you fucking fake ass junk boy.
Yeah, come pull up boy, come pull up.
All right, let's come through this way.
Let's talk and do this.
I'm not talking to you.
Okay, yeah, really come to Toronto now.
Really come to Toronto, pussy boy.
Don't remember, I'll see you around kid.
I'm a fucking let you open them hollows.
I swear to God I will.
Show me.
I'm a mom's life and I ain't a federal little boy.
I'm streaming right now, pussy boy.
Yeah, come to Toronto.
Record this, bitch boy.
Record this, pussy boy.
That could have scored like a good little bitch.
Record like a good little bitch.
Incredible stuff, riveting really.
I don't know the whole lore here of everything that happened.
That seems like some real degenerate shit across the board.
But I will say that insult of like record like a good little bitch.
That falls really flat when you yourself are also recording.
You brother, you're streaming it.
That's two sides of the same coin.
In fact, that's a step above recording it.
Not exactly the optimal insult there.
You kind of took some self-sustained damage on that one too.
You hurt yourself in the confusion there as well.
Since that also included you.
But anyway, I just wanted to talk about this guy
because I just can't fucking stand him.
I think that this is completely unacceptable behavior
to just be abusing your dog on stream.
I think that shit super sucks.
That's about it.
See ya.